happy new year
The first batten of the new year is
I did a new year's writing project.
I thought writing down my resolutions was the end of it.
The topic came up and before I knew it I was feeling very excited.
I look forward to working with you again this year.
Batten Girl Squad's Inside Out Batten
happy new year
congratulations
How is it, everyone, the new year is here?
It all changed all at once
This is what 2025 is.
2024 and 2025 will be completely different.
No.
I guess it's 4 to 5
The number that changes when you purchase a preview
Certainly
Sorry, sorry, sorry
I want to stay young
Now this time
congratulations
This is the first post in the new year for Urabatten, so I started writing to everyone.
I've been to Kakizome, yes. Is it a master's school or something? It's not like that.
Does that mean?
Well then, the first thing I'll ask you to write about is abundance in 2025.
How about that? Yes, yes.
I'll take out the eclerator.
Terun
Wait a minute, I might be small too.
I was able to write it
uncle
Here are my resolutions for 2025
I wrote Taisei
I think it will be a year of big changes for the group as well.
I chose this because I wanted it to be a year of great growth.
I will do my best
uncle
Yes, my resolution for 2025 is to evolve.
This year is also the year when Batten Girls' Corps will have a new structure.
Personally, I am 17 to 18 years old, which is the year when I turn from a child to an adult.
I chose this because I wanted to be able to evolve myself in many ways.
I will do my best.
yes.
Old man
Here are Rikko Ueda's resolutions for 2025.
I'm new to Jajan.
This is amazing, and this is what I felt in 2024 as well.
I think it's really important to work hard without forgetting your original intentions.
As everyone has said, there will be a new system.
Of course all the newer members are like that too.
I hope that the five of us can move forward happily without forgetting our original intentions.
brother
Yes! Here are Lila's resolutions for 2025!
I'm an adult!
At the age of 18, you become an adult and join the ranks of adults.
And now that we have new members, we feel like we're a bit more senior members.
I will do my best to do the adult part even more!
Kiya's love's resolution for 2025 is
It's the heart!
I think we all want to work hard as one, and let's live our lives with care for our hearts.
Yes, that's the end of it.
Okay, everyone, continue.
Yay!
what?
Not just one.
Aspirations for 2030.
30 years!?
Eh, how old are you?
Yay!
It's the future.
What should I do, 30 years?
30 years?
What?30?
30?
It's early
I don't understand at all
Is it in the respirology area?People in water
You look the saddest
Did you look sad?
No, it's fine
Imagine yourself in 2030
I'm in now
in 2030
Yes, my resolution for 2030 is
here
It's independent
After all, 5 years later
I'm 23 years old now.
I'm already 20 years old
3 years have passed
yes
I hope that they will become independent and fine adults.
become independent
My aspirations for 2030 are
It's life
I'm turning 30 so
life's big thing
Tan
Feels like a ning point
By the time I reach 30 years, I think my career as an artist will have been very long.
Thinking about how your life is going is a way of looking forward to it. I made it
Yay
Yes, my resolution for 2030 is
strongly
what?
soft
It's soft, but I couldn't win.
Something flew away
I needed a little more here, and I made a mistake when I wrote it, but this is the kind of person I am. With the goal of becoming
Because I have an image, by the time I reach the age of 29 in 2030, I will have become a person who suits these words. I thought it was nice so I chose this.
I think yes
That blue one
me in the blue building
me
The way to do it in 2030 is to rain in the bright light.
I don't know what the future will be like in 5 years, if not 30 years. I want to do my best with a bright and smiling face, so I'm cheerful.
my
The goal for 2030 is AI Echo A
Love, love, love, good. If you say 30 years from now, it will be about 10 years. Years from now, this will probably be something like AI.
I think that is also developing ai It's a love that means that it's okay to be yourself or be yourself.
Daddy's bag
I won't lose to AI.Okay, here's the final question.
large
Boo Boo will be released in 2030 and will be a big hit. That new song will be released in 2030. What is the single title?
What's going on?
5 years from now.
surely
It was released five years later and became a huge hit.
Eh, then what should we do?
I don't really think of anything
Well, Ai-chan will drop it for me.
No, no, let's stop and go from here.
It feels easy, isn't it?
Ai-chan early
That's right, it's early.
When I think about it, I don't understand.
No, it's a genius line
Easy to understand
2 people please do not discuss
sorry
think for yourself
Released in 2030 and a huge hit
What is the title of Basho's new single?
15 years old
That heart is
This song was released when I thought it was Basho's 15th anniversary year.
Sticking to the boys and girls of the world
It will also touch adults who are nostalgic for that era.
A huge hit throughout Japan
It's quite different from the choral songs that I've heard, but it's a bit like that. You have an image, right?
It would be great if a famous song that would be sung at graduation ceremonies was created for Erased.
What is the title of the new single that will be released in 2030 and will be a huge hit?
We, Battensha, have been asked to make a debut song in 2020. I released a song called Oisha, and since then it's been the best in the last 5 years.
I think words like superlatives have become quite popular. When that happens, the next thing that will become popular is that which represents the superlative.
I think I have to go with the best one. Well, it's been 10 years since the release of Oisa.
I'm sure you'll conquer the world with your songs.
I think! Let's do our best!
Hey there!
What is the title of Nussho's new single, which will be released in 2030 and become a big hit?
top star
I am confident that in five years, we will definitely become the brightest top stars in Japan, the world, and the universe. Because
Please listen to the new single Top Star that will be heard everywhere on this planet.
Wait, wait, wait
What is the title of the new single that will be released in 2030 and will be a huge hit?
I can't lose to AI
It's a heart
I think there will be a lot of AI coming out in 2030.
Why are you scared of AI? Is it okay?
With the meaning that everyone should live their own way
When I put it on, it sold.
It's empathy
That's right
Please listen to it as much as you can.
So, please support Batten Girls' Team again this year.
thank you